<resources>
	<string name="app_name">"JHL &amp; KM's Restaurant Finder"</string>
	<string name="title_activity_maps">"Restaurant Location"</string>

	<!--main activity-->
	<string name="main_instructions_header_lbl">"JHL &amp; KM\'s\nRestaurant Finder (っ˘ڡ˘ς)"</string>
	<string name="main_instructions_body_txt">"\"Are you new to Toronto?\"\n\n\"Do you have an insatiable palate that cannot be satisfied by plebeian grub?\"\n\n\"Do you have an unquenchable thirst for juices to fill your holes and seep through your dark cavities?\"\n\nIf you answered yes to any of the questions above, you are in the right place ♪♪ ヽ(ˇ∀ˇ )ゞ!\n\nThis application will show you a list of restaurants found in Toronto, ON, Canada, based upon the type of cuisine you select on the next screen.\n\nNow that we have your attention, let us begin without further ado!"
	</string>
	<string name="main_continue_btn_lbl">"Let\'s Go! ヽ(´▽`)/"</string>
	<string name="main_continue_btn_clicked_txt">"Marching onwards ᕕ( ᐛ )ᕗ!"</string>

	<!--cuisine list activity-->
	<string name="cuisine_list_title">"Cuisines List"</string>
	<string name="cuisine_list_instructions_txt">"Here in Toronto, we may have many delicacies which may not be found anywhere else!\n\nPlease click on one of the following types of cuisines to see the restaurants for that particular cuisine type:"</string>

	<!--restaurant list-->
	<string name="restaurant_list_title">"Restaurants List"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_show_btn_lbl">"Show"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_instructions_txt">"If you like what you see, please click on one of the restaurants below to see the location of the restaurant on a map.\n\nAlternatively, you can select another cuisine  type from the drop down list below and click on the \"Show\" Button to see the restaurants for that particular cuisine type."</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_american_sel_txt">"This is America ヽ( •_)ᕗ"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_asian_sel_txt">"Looking for some exotic flavors (｡◕‿◕｡)?"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_breakfast_sel_txt">"Just woke up and ready for some food 눈_눈"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_chinese_sel_txt">"给我好吃的 ฅ^•ﻌ•^ฅ"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_indian_sel_txt">"I want to feel the burn tomorrow щ（ﾟДﾟщ）!"</string>
	<string name="restaurant_list_italian_sel_txt">"Dammi buon appetito ಠ‿ಠ"</string>
	<string name="toggle_view">Toggle View</string>
</resources>
